<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scene on Wander and Wonder</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/scene/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scene on Wander and Wonder</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/scene/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Croatia</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Croatia is an underrated gem in Europe with a stunning coastline, rich history, and a vibrant food scene. Whether it’s sailing the Adriatic Sea, exploring ancient towns, or hiking in national parks, Croatia has something for every traveler.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why it’s a must-do&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pristine beaches: The Dalmatian Coast boasts some of the clearest waters in Europe.&#xA;Historic cities: Dubrovnik, also known as the “Pearl of the Adriatic,” offers an enchanting blend of ancient architecture and modern luxuries.&#xA;Island hopping: Explore the thousands of islands scattered along the coast.&#xA;Best time to go&#xA;May to September when the weather is warm and ideal for swimming.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bike Ride on the Amalfi Coast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Amalfi Coast is one of Italy’s most breathtaking stretches of coastline. Winding roads carved into cliffs offer stunning views of the Mediterranean Sea, quaint fishing villages, and terraced vineyards. Taking a bike ride here is not just a journey, but an adventure of a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why it’s a must-do&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scenic Beauty: Every twist and turn reveals a new postcard-worthy view.&#xA;Challenging yet rewarding: The route is ideal for cyclists looking for both a physical challenge and mesmerizing scenery.&#xA;Cultural exploration: Along the way, you can stop by small towns like Positano and Ravello to explore ancient architecture, art, and local cuisine.&#xA;Best time to go&#xA;April to June or September to October, when the weather is pleasant, and the crowds are fewer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
